Serhiy Shainyuk

Front-End Developer

- sj.shaynyuk@gmail.com
- Sh.Sergiy
- +3 8(063) 443-83-18
- SergiGan/HubFrEnd
- Lviv, Ukraine



First of all, experience is, a collection of everything that happens to a person in her life and that she is conscious; people can have experience about themselves, their abilities, their virtues and vices, and people can also have experience and ideas, ideas and knowledge. So I'm open to people if they are ready for it, to knowledge, experience and everything new that makes the world a better one. I strive for excellence, critical thinking, versatility in their interests. I am interested in the latest technologies, in particular in the field of information technology, as well as software optimization and participation in its development. Motivation by the challengei and non-standard tasks. Why in IT, is because modern life can not be imagined without the latest technology and self-improvement.

SKILLs

Software

HTML/CSS

mastered by 85%

Bootstrap

mastered by 70%

JavaScript

mastered by 55%

JQuery

50%

Angular 7*)

ng7example some works

Python 3

35%

Fortran

70%

Sublime Text

mastered by 85%

Quoda

I use 65%

Koala

85%

DreamViewer

got skills 80%

Photoshop

70%

AutoCad

65%

3DPipe

90%

PC Stadyo

90%

ANSYS/Mechanical/Structural

35%

Education

SkillUp IT Specialist Training Center Angular 7 *2019

SkillUp IT Specialist Training Center Front-End 2019

This is a Ukrainian public project for mass open online

"Prometheus" courses

The course of "Fundamentals of Information Security"

2015

Ivan Franko Lviv National University Faculty of Physics and Electronics, physics specialist

2001-2006

Experience

PrAT "TehEnergo" Leading Engineer in the diagnostics department of the equipment



PrAT "LvivOrgres"

Engineer for Safe Maintenance of Power Equipment

2008-2016

Publishing House "World of Physics"

Text layout and editing

2006-2008